Guide to the Ralph W. Cummings Papers
Ralph W. Cummings Papers
- Professional Papers, 1952-1997; 1952 1997; 33.5 linear feet
  - Research and Related Materials, 1952-1997
    - WAAR - workshop Conotou Participants, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - WAAR - workshop Conotou Agenda, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - WAAR - workshop Conotou follow-up, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - WAARR Research Papers (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - WAARR Research Papers (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - IARC correspondence about WAARR report content, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - ILCA Internal Publications (1 of 5), 1991-1992 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - ILCA Internal Publications (2 of 5), 1991-1992 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - ILCA Internal Publications (3 of 5), 1991-1992 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - ILCA Internal Publications (4 of 5), 1991-1992 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - ILCA Internal Publications (5 of 5), 1991-1992 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - ILCA Annual Report, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Eastern and Southern Africa Agricultural Research Review World Bank, 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - West Africa Crops Research Review Mission Peer Review Work (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - West Africa Crops Research Review Mission Peer Review Work (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - ILCA Correspondence (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - ILCA Correspondence (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Tree crops Report - Draft with notes (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Tree crops Report - Draft with notes (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - ICRAF - An Introduction to Agroforestry Diagnostics and Design, [198?] (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - ILCA Board of Trustees Administrative Literature and Notes, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - John Dillon Board Papers, 1987-1988 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - ILCA Board of Trustees Nominations Committee, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Board of Directors General Literature Various Authors (1 of 2), 1979-1984 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Board of Directors General Literature Various Authors (2 of 2), 1979-1984 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - ICRAF Board Meeting, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - CGIAR and ICRAF joint board meeting (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - CGIAR and ICRAF joint board meeting (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - ICRAF 15th board meeting Nairobi (1 of 3), 1988 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - ICRAF 15th board meeting Nairobi (2 of 3), 1988 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - ICRAF 15th board meeting Nairobi (3 of 3), 1988 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - ICRAF 16th board meeting (1 of 3), 1989 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - ICRAF 16th board meeting (2 of 3), 1989 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - ICRAF 16th board meeting (3 of 3), 1989 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - ICAR reorganization mid 1960s notes and papers (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - CGIAR TAC meetings 1-4, 1971-1972 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - CGIAR TAC meetings 5-7, 1973-1974 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - CGIAR TAC meetings 8-10, 1974-1975 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - CGIAR TAC meetings 11-12, 1975-1976 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - CGIAR TAC meetings 13-15, 1976-1977 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - CGIAR TAC meetings 22-24, 1979-1980 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - CGIAR TAC meetings 25-27, 1981-1982 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - CGIAR TAC meetings 28-30, 1982-1983 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - CGIAR TAC meetings 31-32, 1983-1984 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - CGIAR TAC meetings 33-35, 1984-1985 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - CGIAR TAC meetings 37-38 and 41-42, 1985-1987 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - CGIAR TAC meetings 43, 44, 45 and 47, 1987-1989 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - CGIAR TAC meetings 48-52, 1989-1990 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - CGIAR TAC meetings 53, 57, 58 and 60, 1991-1993 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - CGIAR TAC 15th meeting agenda notebook (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - CGIAR TAC 15th meeting agenda notebook (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - ICRAF Financial Nairobi, 1990-1991 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - ICRAF 2nd draft program of work for 1984 with projections for 1985-1987 (1 of 2) (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - ICRAF 2nd draft program of work for 1984 with projections for 1985-1987 (2 of 2) (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - ICRAF Directors Progress Report, 1984-1987 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - ICRAF Directors Progress Report, 1987-1989 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - ICRAF correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - ICRAF staff policy manual drafts, 1986-1987 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - ICRAF professional staff list, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - ICRAF annual accounts reports, 1986-1989 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - ICRAF Price Waterhouse board reports, 1985-1989 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - ICRAF Budgets, 1987-1993 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - ICRAF meeting minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - ICRAF meeting minutes, 1986-1989 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - ICRAF meeting minutes, 1989-1991 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - ICRAF field station papers Machakos, Kenya, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - ICRAF charter and mission writing, [1978?] (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - ICRAF programs and projections, 1981-1983 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - ICRAF publications bibliographies, 1978-1984 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Ford Foundation Employment, 1972-1976 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - World Food Prize Nomination, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller Foundation New Delhi, 1969-1971 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - North Carolina State University Alumni Association Award, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - North Carolina State University Alumni Forever Club (1 of 2), 1987-1997 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - North Carolina State University Alumni Forever Club (2 of 2), 1987-1997 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Ohio State University Alumni Award, 1986-1996 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Ohio State University Alumni Award correspondence, 1991-1997 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Punjab Agricultural University Honorary Degree, 1970 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Presidential End Hunger Awards, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Soil Science Society of America Distinguished Service Award, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - NCSU Honorary Degree, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - "Climate Change and Agricultural Production in Non-industrial Countries" by Lloyd Slater, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - CGIAR 25th Anniversary, 1996 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Pakistan wheat study (1 of 2), 1977-1983 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Pakistan wheat study (2 of 2), 1977-1983 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - ILCA correspondence (1 of 3), 1986-1992 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - ILCA correspondence (2 of 3), 1986-1992 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - ILCA correspondence (3 of 3), 1986-1992 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Ford Foundation Consultancy IIMI, 1982-1984 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Proposal for International Crops research Institute (ICRISAT) manuscript with edits, 1971 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Ernest Nunn Ph.D. Thesis, "Organization and Management for the Support of Agricultural Research at the Research Institute Level", 1983 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Ernest Nunn PhD. Thesis "Organization and Management for the Support of Agricultural Research at the Research Institute Level", 1983 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - CGIAR 18th TAC Meeting Report (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - CGIAR 18th TAC Meeting Report (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Academic Publications, 1968 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Conference Papers and Talks (1 of 2), 1967-1979 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Conference Papers and Talks (2 of 2), 1967-1979 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Ralph W. Cummings Jr. Academic Writing (1 of 3), 1965-1979 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Ralph W. Cummings Jr. Academic Writing (2 of 3), 1965-1979 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Ralph W. Cummings Jr. Academic Writing (3 of 3), 1965-1979 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Aquaculture Aid Projects (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Aquaculture Aid Projects (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Asian Association of Agricultural Universities (AAAU) correspondence, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - ICRISAT origins and structure, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - ICARDA Aleppo Syria Research Station, unknown (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Aquaculture notes and correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Group Photographs, [195?-1991] (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Speeches and Talks published, 1967-1974 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Speeches and Talks, 1967-1975 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Speeches and Talks typescripts, 1975-1980 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Agricultural Universities in India (1 of 2), 1962-1963 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Agricultural Universities in India (2 of 2), 1962-1963 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - The Madras Agricultural Journal, 1961 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Soil Science Society of America, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Watauga Medal Awarded, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Watauga Medal nomination, 1984 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - ICRISAT proposal for research of groundnuts, 1974 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - ICRISAT Expectations for Future Developments in Sorghum Millets and Legumes, 1976 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - ICRISAT "Address on the Passing Out Function', 1976 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - ICRISAT correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - "Overseas Mission" radio show transcripts and photo, 1975 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - North Carolina State University Employment Papers, 1966-1971 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - ILCA Administrative Papers, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - ISNAR review - Pakistan, 1982 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - CGIAR 16th TAC meeting report (1 of 3), 1977 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - CGIAR 16th TAC meeting report (2 of 3), 1977 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - CGIAR 16th TAC meeting report (3 of 3), 1977 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - ICRISAT correspondence, 1982 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Peer Clippings, [1952-1996?] (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Speeches, 1968-1983 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Printed Speeches (1 of 3), 1968-1984 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Printed Speeches (2 of 3), 1968-1984 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Printed Speeches (3 of 3), 1968-1984 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - CGIAR TAC secretariat 19th program draft commentaries (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - CGIAR TAC secretariat 19th program draft commentaries (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Ford Foundation UK Visit, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller Foundation Correspondence, 1957-1963 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Ralph W Cummings Jr. World Hunger Report, 1981 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - International Society of Soil Science, 1950 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - "RF" Newsletters, 1984-1985 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Pakistan wheat study, oversized documents, 1977-1983 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - International maps and newspapers, [1970-1989?] (Flatfile 4)